good morning welcome to the spacious
早上好，欢迎来到宽敞的
project jigsaw hack
项目拼图黑客
and there are plenty of seats down front
而且前面有很多座位
just to warn you but this will be QA
只是警告您，但这将是质量检查
and if you want to ask a question we
如果您想提一个问题，我们
will ask you to use the microphone here
会要求您在这里使用麦克风
so that everyone can hear and so all the
这样每个人都能听到，所以所有
people lovely people on the Internet can
互联网上可爱的人可以
hear so if you plan to ask questions
听到，如果你打算问问题
sitting in the front could be to our
坐在前面可能是我们的
advantage on the other hand if you want
另一方面，如果你想要
the exercise you can sit in the back so
你可以坐在后面做运动
hi I'm mark Reinhold this is Alan
嗨，我是马克·莱因霍尔德，我是艾伦
Bateman and Mandy Chung we all work on
Bateman和Mandy Chung我们都在努力
project jigsaw along with a few other
项目拼图以及其他一些项目
people like Alex Buckley who couldn't be
像Alex Buckley这样的人
here this morning a quick reminder of
今天早上在这里快速提醒
the multitude of sessions we have sadly
可悲的是，我们有很多次会议
a few of these are in the past and at
其中一些是过去和现在
this point you can catch them on video
这一点你可以在视频上捕捉到他们
other than in person however the
除了亲自以外
introduction to modular development will
模块化开发简介将
be repeated today at 3 advanced at 4:30
今天3点4:30被重复
and modules and services tomorrow
以及明天的模块和服务
afternoon at 2 p.m.
下午2点
just a quick survey how many people have
快速调查一下有多少人
been to intro already good how many
去过介绍已经好多少
people have been to advanced good how
人们去过先进如何
many people have been to modules and
很多人去过模块和
services guys it's sort of diminishing
服务人员，这正在减少
returns here ok well that's good you you
回到这里好吧，那对你好
you have more chances let's see what
你有更多的机会让我们看看
else do we got information if you've
否则，我们是否能获得信息
seen slides like this already since
从那以后就已经看到过这样的幻灯片
you've been to the the earlier talks we
您去过较早的会谈
have extensive documentation although a
有大量的文档，尽管
lot of it is fairly dense in in one two
一二之中很多都比较密集
three four five different jep's jdk
三四五不同的jep的jdk
enhancement proposals you can find links
您可以找到增强建议链接
to those on the jigsaw project page
到拼图项目页面上的人
there's also jsr 376 which is also
还有jsr 376，
linked to from the jigsaw project page
从拼图项目页面链接到
in particular there's a document called
特别是有一个文件叫做
state of the module system which is a a
模块系统的状态为aa
summary of all of the essential features
所有基本功能的摘要
of the module system one more joke I'm
模块系统的另一个笑话
reminded 282 right okay there did the J
提醒282对，那里的J
link JEP 282 should've added that sorry
链接JEP 282应该添加对不起
okay uh we work for Oracle questions
好吧，我们为Oracle问题工作
please you can come to the mic if you're
请如果你是
shy you can tweet at me if you're but
害羞，如果你在
you know I mean we're all we're all
你知道我是说我们就是我们
friends here right there aren't that
这里的朋友不是
many people everything everything that
很多人所有的一切
happens in the room stays in the room
发生在房间里停留在房间里
okay we're done
好，我们完成了
that mic please
请那个麦克风
so I worked in a security engineering
所以我从事安全工程
team and one of the problems we run into
团队和我们遇到的问题之一
is that some api's are for general use
是一些api是通用的
and some are prone to misuse so putting
有些容易被滥用，因此放置
if you you can export the packages that
如果您可以导出软件包
are prone to misuse as which allows you
容易被滥用，因为这使您
to kind of whitelist who consumes them
归类为消耗他们的白名单
nicely but a lot of times if the export
很好，但很多时候，如果出口
as declarations are being maintained by
因为声明由
the library authors they may not have an
他们可能没有图书馆作者
exhaustive list especially if this is
详尽的清单，特别是如果这是
kind of part of some kind of open source
某种开源的一部分
security product so is there a way to
安全产品，有没有办法
kind of be right at when you're bundling
捆绑在一起时是正确的
an application the exports as oh and
一个应用程序将导出为
they may be based on some so basically
他们可能是基于一些基本的
you you you you you and that you imagine
你，你，你，你，你在想像
having a module that somebody else made
有别人制作的模块
and you want to change his exports
你想改变他的出口
because you know better than they do
因为你比他们更了解
would you mind
你会介意的
sure I've come to come before the mic
确保我来了麦克风之前
please so I have a class called
请给我上一堂课
unchecked conversions which is provides
提供的未经检查的转化
factory methods for a type that
类型的工厂方法
encapsulates a security property so it's
封装了安全属性，因此
it's if you think if you know
如果你想知道
trademarking in the security context and
在安全范围内注册商标，以及
so uncheck conversions is prone to
因此取消选中转换很容易
misuse if somebody just you know follows
如果您认识的某人误用了
their autocomplete sorry so this is this
他们的自动填充功能很抱歉，这是这个
is a this is a class that you created
是这是您创建的类
yes
是
what can you just not export it I know
你能不出口什么我知道
can I just pick up one thing you you you
我可以拿起一件事吗
you use you said in your question
你用你在问题中说的
auto-corrected so I'm assuming you
自动更正，所以我假设你
actually mean the IDE which probably
实际上是指IDE
doesn't know about modules yet has gone
不知道有关模块的信息
and auto-completed and putting the
并自动完成，然后将
method name i yeah i'm using
方法名称，是的，我正在使用
autocomplete as a way to refer to kind
自动完成作为一种指称方式
of a naive user finds this API okay so
天真的用户发现此API可以，因此
this is an API that you created in a
这是您在
model that you maintain yeah and you
你维持的模型，你
need to export it to some other modules
需要将其导出到其他模块
but not yeah so for example I might have
但是不是，例如，我可能有
a type safe HTML which is a fragment of
类型安全的HTML，它是
HTML that is safe to embedded in
可安全嵌入的HTML
applications domain run I have a
应用程序域运行我有一个
template system that might produce this
可能会产生这种情况的模板系统
that's a third party I have an sanitizer
那是第三方，我有洗手液
which was script tags and element stats
这是脚本标签和元素统计
and so a project lead might say I trust
所以项目负责人可能会说我相信
the people who wrote the template system
编写模板系统的人
I trust the people who maintain the
我相信维护
sanitizer
消毒剂
I want my developers to use safe HTML I
我希望我的开发人员使用安全的HTML
don't want the large group of
不想大批
application developers right right so so
应用程序开发人员正确的如此
right so a qualified expert not I'm
对，所以我不是一个合格的专家
sorry I'm horribly ignorant it's
对不起，我太无知了
qualified experts different from exports
与出口不同的合格专家
as
如
there well no sorry there's no exports
那里不对不起没有出口
out so you can export a export to
出来，所以您可以将公鸡出口导出到
the ISA note that you started sorry
ISA记录，您开始感到抱歉
export to that is qualified expose so
出口到合格暴露所以
you can say exports Fuu when that
你可以说出口福
exports package food to anybody who any
出口包装食品给任何人
other module that requires your module
需要您的模块的其他模块
yeah or you can say exports food to bar
是的，或者您可以说将食物出口到酒吧
comma baz whatever and only modules
逗号baz无论什么，只有模块
named bar and baz can can access that
名为bar和baz的用户可以访问
alright and and so my question was the
好吧，所以我的问题是
safe HTML i want to export this
安全的HTML我想导出这个
unchecked conversions the package
未经检查的转换包
containing unchecked conversions to the
包含未经检查的转化
sanitizer to the template system right
对模板系统进行消毒的权利
all three of these the safe HTML
所有这三个都是安全的HTML
definition these are all open source
定义这些都是开源的
projects and i want to do that exports
项目，我想做出口
to without you know if i have to i'll
到没有你知道我是否要
rewrite the safe HTML bundle said that
重写安全的HTML捆绑软件说
the definition okay but yeah got it
定义不错，但是知道了
so our our general philosophy is is
所以我们的总体理念是
though is that it's best to respect the
虽然是最好的尊重
original intent of the module author
模块作者的初衷
right where we're putting a lot more
就在我们投入更多的地方
power into the hands of someone who
权力掌握在某人手中
maintains a component so that they can
维护组件，以便他们可以
say i want to export this and not that
说我想出口这个而不是那个
and that's that's that's kind of primary
这就是主要的
however yes there are times when you
但是是的，有时候你
when you need to break that when one
当你需要打破的时候
crude way is on the command line if
粗略的方法是在命令行上
you're in a scenario where you're you're
你处在一个场景中
you're writing you're you're in some
你在写，你在写
kind of container or you're writing
那种容器或者你在写
writing some kind of kind of container
写某种容器
and you have the opportunity you can
你有机会可以
certainly you can rewrite module input
当然可以重写模块输入
class files as you load them you know
加载文件时知道的类文件
it's a class file and sm already already
这是一个班级文件并且sm已经
an already understands them so if you
一个已经了解他们，所以如果你
really want to you could intercept them
真的很想你可以拦截他们
you know if you if you if you write the
你知道如果你写的话
code that that creates the class letters
创建班级字母的代码
it loads of those then you can intercept
它加载那些然后你可以拦截
them on the on the way in and go change
他们在途中去改变
their exports if you want to or if
他们的出口，如果你想或
you're comfortable editing binary
您可以轻松编辑二进制文件
artifacts which
文物
I mean I'd rather not do in a production
我的意思是我不想在生产中做
environment but some people like to like
环境但是有些人喜欢
to do that you can you can certainly you
做到这一点就可以，当然可以
know get the jar file off central or
知道把jar文件移到中央或
wear it wherever you're getting it and
随身携带它
go modify modify that and then put that
去修改修改那个，然后把那个
in your archive and and deploy that but
在您的档案中并部署
there's there's no there's intentionally
那里没有故意
no API that makes it trivial to go and
没有让它变得微不足道的API，
basically violate the wishes of the
基本上违反了
module author because we think that's
模块作者，因为我们认为
important too we think it's important
同样重要，我们认为这很重要
for there to be sort of a threshold that
有一定的门槛
you know a barrier of resistance there
你知道那里的抵抗障碍
because it ought to be discouraged no
因为不应该阻止它
there's no there's no level of
没有没有层次的
indirection we're we're a sufficiently
间接我们是我们足够
forward-thinking module author could
有远见的模块作者可以
could think oh well maybe you know some
会想，哦，也许你知道一些
of my users will want to do this and put
我的用户将要这样做并放入
in a placeholder and then have it there
在占位符中，然后放在那里
there's a navigate filled in by the
有一个导航由
module system later that's a level of
稍后的模块系统
configurability that you know I think it
您知道我认为的可配置性
is interesting to think about but we
很有趣，但是我们
need to get one zero out and you know
需要得到一个零，你知道
after after some years of experience
经过几年的经验
maybe we have we would add something
也许我们要添加一些东西
like that maybe but it's it it
这样也许吧，就是这样
definitely feels like the sort of thing
绝对感觉像是种东西
that we would need a lot more experience
我们需要更多的经验
to justify so you know it's it's always
证明是正确的，所以你知道它总是
a bit harrowing designing something like
设计类似的东西有点费劲
this no matter how hard you try to think
不管你怎么努力思考
forward you're gonna miss miss stuff and
转发你会想念小姐的东西，
so we try to keep you know try to keep
所以我们尽量让您知道尝试保持
it simple to start see what people's
轻松开始了解人们的
experiences are refine it over you know
经验使您对它有所了解
the next few major releases
接下来的几个主要版本
no more questions
别再问问题了
Liat please come come up to the mic
利亚特请来麦克风
so I was actually in the introductory
所以我实际上是在介绍
buy one of the people working on the
买一个工作的人
project but in the pre conf so that
项目，但在预conf，这样
might have been discussing it would
可能一直在讨论
actually but if you can give a bit of
实际上，但是如果您能给一点
detail about how how it's going to work
有关其如何工作的详细信息
that you can use two different versions
您可以使用两个不同的版本
of the same module so let's say you know
相同的模块，所以假设您知道
we have who said you could do that sorry
我们有谁说你可以那样做对不起
wait III I'm not familiar what would
等我不知道会怎样
what is pre comps like the day before
前一天的预告片是什么样的
Java one story so there was I was giving
Java一个故事，所以我给了
the presentation I can take it up I'm
演示文稿我可以拿起来我
just curious because none of us were
只是好奇，因为我们都不是
there yeah there's like day before it
是的，就像前一天一样
was on Sunday and there it was mentioned
在星期天，在那里有人提到
that so right now we have the problem
所以现在我们有问题
right that you for example nettie okay I
对的，例如你，nettie好吧，我
have three different libraries that use
有三个不同的库使用
different versions of nettie and they
不同版本的nettie，它们
collide so I have elasticsearch I have a
碰撞，所以我有elasticsearch我有一个
zookeeper client and I have a CH DP
动物园管理员客户，我有CH DP
client all of them used in unity in
客户所有在团结中使用
different versions and okay so and how
不同的版本，好吧，如何
do you handle this today currently a jar
你今天处理这个吗
jar and with a lot of pain I repackage
罐子，我很痛苦地重新包装
them it's it's awful it's it's it's
他们是可怕的是
often you need to upload those binaries
通常您需要上传这些二进制文件
repackage with you know so it's often
重新包装与您知道，所以经常
but I'm so so so in your final
但我在决赛中如此
application you have three different
您有三种不同的应用
copies of Nettie yes at least two of
Nettie的副本是至少两个
which have been haven't had all their
还没有全部
packages renamed yes I'm so sorry yes so
软件包重命名为是，很抱歉，是这样
and this works yeah at the end and then
这在最后是有效的，然后
it works but it's painful and it's
它有效，但很痛苦，而且
error-prone because people can use you
容易出错，因为人们可以使用您
know different because it's because we
知道不同是因为我们
don't have the multi system quality then
那么就没有多系统质量
everything is exposed people can use
一切都暴露了人们可以使用
this version of a C and that musician so
这个版本的C和那个音乐家
so it works so the so the easy answer
这样就可以了，所以很容易回答
for me to give is pick one no but I
我给的是选一个，但我
can't I can't because they're binary
我不能，因为它们是二进制的
incompatible and I need that feature
不兼容，我需要该功能
from elasticsearch and in that feature
来自elasticsearch以及该功能
from zookeeper and that feature from a
来自Zookeeper，而该功能来自
sexy big light right sir
性感大灯右先生
so jigsaw is not going to solve that
所以拼图是不会解决的
that that isn't that is not the design
那不是那不是设计
center for for the platform module
平台模块中心
system
系统
there there are facilities that allow
有设施允许
you to have multiple versions of a
您有一个的多个版本
module of the same name in the system
系统中同名的模块
but they're fairly advanced and they're
但他们相当先进，他们
they're designed for for people who are
他们是专为那些谁是
writing containers you know app servers
编写您知道应用服务器的容器
or test harnesses or things that things
或测试线束或事物
that have the the have at least enough
具有至少
sophistication that they're doing their
他们在做自己的事的老练
own doing their own class loaders we
自己做自己的类加载器
made an intentional design decision not
没有做出故意的设计决定
to try to handle the multiple version
尝试处理多个版本
problem because doing that in in
问题，因为在
generality brings a ton of complexity
普遍性带来大量复杂性
and you wind up you end up with those GI
然后你结束了那些胃肠道
yeah so oh so that was actually
是的，哦，那实际上是
discussed at that session I asked him it
在那次会议上讨论过，我问他
sounds like like OSGi done right and he
听起来像OSGi做得对，他
said it's different but it can give you
说不同，但可以给你
like a lot of the same value series
就像很多相同的价值系列
saying not not easily so I need to write
说不容易，所以我需要写
so so they're there there's a there's a
所以他们在那里有一个
concept called called layers and if
这个概念叫做层，如果
you've been to the advanced talk or you
您去过高级讲座或
could still go to the invented I might
仍然可以去发明
go yeah you can learn about layers and
是的，您可以了解图层和
if you if you're you know in a situation
如果你知道的话
like yours where you really had to do
像你真正需要做的
this one approach would be for you to
这一种方法适合您
load each version of nettie you know
加载您知道的nettie的每个版本
along with the particular thing
与特定的事物一起
elasticsearch or whatever that needed to
elasticsearch或任何需要
use it into its own layer with its own
将其用于自己的图层
class motor right you know we we
一流的汽车，对吧，我们知道
actually we have api's that make me that
实际上我们有api使我
if you if you just need fairly
如果您只是需要
garden-variety
花园品种
class loaders then you can very easily
类加载器，那么您可以非常轻松地
make a layer and and be that it feed
铺一层，然后喂
that ISM be as input into the resolver
将ISM作为解析器的输入
so it's not hard to do it's not like it
所以不难做到不喜欢它
takes thousand a thousand lines of code
需要一千行代码
you can probably do it in a few doesn't
你大概可以做到
but it is sort of a more sophisticated
但这有点复杂
approach okay thank you actually I
方法好吧谢谢我
should actually think that that might
实际上应该认为那可能
like you said also for test harnesses
就像你所说的测试线束
because one of the problems that we have
因为我们遇到的问题之一
is that we've had several times where
是我们已经有几次
applications deploy we embed jet in our
应用程序部署，我们将喷气机嵌入我们的
own runnable jars and applications went
自己的可运行罐子和应用程序去了
to production without having the my
没有我的生产
sequel connector because during testing
后继连接器，因为在测试过程中
people had my signature in scope test
人们在范围测试中得到了我的签名
and maven
和行家
and everything worked because the the
一切正常，因为
the classpath is shared but then when
类路径是共享的，但是当
they came to a production it failed so I
他们来了一个失败的作品，所以我
might be able to use layers also yeah
也许还可以使用图层
layers could also also be useful there
层也可能在这里有用
and wait yeah we already we use layers
等一下，我们已经在使用图层了
in in the JT reg test harness and open
在JT reg测试工具中并打开
JDK we use the you know Java C uses if
JDK我们使用Java C所使用的
you have an annotation processor the
你有一个注释处理器
Java C and JDK 9 loads those into into a
Java C和JDK 9将它们加载到
layer it's not particularly difficult
层并不特别困难
okay so you can you you can certainly do
好吧，所以你可以，你当然可以做
that as a little bit a bit of backstory
有点背景故事
in that and to fill in some of the
在那并填写一些
philosophical picture in the you know
你知道的哲学图景
we've been through many rounds of
我们经历了许多回合
prototypes on drink so the first big
饮料原型，所以第一个大
prototype we actually we had we had
我们实际上拥有的原型
version constraints in the language and
语言和版本限制
you know complicated heuristics for for
你知道复杂的启发式
finding the optimal you know version
寻找最佳的您知道的版本
given a set of constraints from from a
从
set of modules in in a perspective model
透视模型中的一组模块
graph and it gets it gets really hairy
图，它变得非常毛茸茸
pretty quickly and a sigh and aside from
很快，除了叹息
not wanting to replicate that that kind
不想复制那种
of complexity in the module system you
模块系统的复杂性
know we it was all it also created
知道我们这就是它的全部创造
tension with one of our other goals
与我们其他目标之一的紧张关系
which is to work well with existing
可以与现有产品很好地配合
build tools so you know maven Gradle all
建立工具，让您知道Maven Gradle全部
these things idea IV or whatever they
这些东西的想法四或任何他们
all have their own way of dealing with
都有自己的应对方式
version conflicts I III understand they
版本冲突，我III理解他们
are not optimal but but they are what
不是最优的，但是它们是什么
they are and you know millions and
他们是，你知道数百万，
millions of developers use them and
数百万开发人员使用它们，
hopefully they'll get better over time
希望他们会随着时间的推移变得更好
whatever we you know if if we did full
不管我们知道是否做满
full version solving in jigsaw that
拼图中的完整版本解决方案
whatever we do wouldn't match what your
我们所做的与您的不符
build system does or we could make it
构建系统可以或我们可以做到
match one of them but not the other you
匹配其中一个而不是另一个
know two or five or whatever and so we
知道两个或五个或任何东西，所以我们
at one point a few years back we just
几年前的某个时刻，我们只是
have this inside wait a minute let's not
让这个里面稍等一下吧
do versions and it simplifies so much
做版本，它简化了很多
stuff so that's that's why we want a
东西，所以这就是为什么我们想要一个
we're where we are today
我们今天就在这里
I'd like to verify the understand
我想验证了解
reflection and how this all works in so
反思以及这一切如何运作
if I'm a Jackson developer obviously I
如果我是杰克逊开发人员，显然
can't know who's going to send me their
不知道谁要寄给我他们的
classes so I can't require them but it
类，所以我不能要求他们，但是
run time so sorry you're working on
运行时间，对不起，您正在努力
Jackson I'm I work on Jax oh yeah oh you
杰克逊（Jackson），我在Jax上工作。
actually didn't know I'm just making
其实不知道我只是在做
this up okay that's fine whatever we
好的，不管我们做什么
make this opportunity develop the
使这个机会发展
advance talk as well this afternoon
今天下午也要提前讲话
Jackson has been it has been a very very
杰克逊一直以来都非常非常
useful example for us well I do
对我们来说很好的例子
something like Jackson okay so at
像杰克逊这样的东西在
runtime if somebody passes me a class or
如果有人通过我上课或
a class name then they would have to
一个类名，那么他们将不得不
export I mean yeah they'd have to recall
出口我的意思是，他们必须记得
well export to me yes and if well or
好出口给我，如果很好，或者
just export to everybody right and if
只是向所有人出口，如果
they wanted to lock that I mean if they
他们想锁定我的意思是如果他们
wanted to open themselves up entirely
想完全开放自己
they could say private so that I could
他们可以说是私人的，这样我可以
reflect and get into private fields and
反映并进入私人领域
things yes so that in that case required
是的，所以在这种情况下需要
isn't really even possible or necessary
甚至根本不是不可能或没有必要
for Jackson right so sorry so the
对杰克逊说的对不起，所以
reflect wreath the way reflection works
反映花圈反射方式的工作方式
it didn't originally work like this but
它本来不是这样工作的，但是
the way reflection works is it it
反射的工作原理就是这样
implicitly adds a reads edge if needed
必要时隐式添加读取边缘
so if you're if you're writing if you're
所以如果你是写作的话
writing Jackson code and you go use you
写杰克逊代码，你去用你
know stuff in Java line reflect and and
知道Java行中的内容反映和
you try to access something in some
您尝试访问某些内容
other module if the module you're in
其他模块（如果您所在的模块）
doesn't already have a read edge to that
还没有阅读优势
module the reflection machinery adds it
反射机械模块添加
for free okay you know I don't know
免费，好吧，你知道我不知道
maybe a year and a half ago we actually
大概一年半以前，我们实际上
we actually didn't have that and so you
我们实际上没有那个，所以你
had to add the read edge manually and
必须手动添加读取边缘，然后
lots of people pointed out that's just
很多人指出
cumbersome so we made it kind of
麻烦，所以我们做到了
automatic right then so what this
自动对吗
requires do for me then is it's like
需要为我做那是
when you're in your case you don't and
在您的情况下，您不会
in your case you don't need it right
在您的情况下，您不需要它
you're doing you're doing reflection
你在做反射
it's all it's it's it's all at runtime
一切就在运行时
and you're
而你
what your and you're not you're you're
你和你不是你是你
also not using just static references
也不仅仅是使用静态引用
from compiled bytecodes
从编译的字节码
right right so you don't need it so but
对对对，所以您不需要它，但是
for things I do require statically you
对于我确实需要你做的事情
know do you have to require for static
知道你需要静态
if you want to compile it yep and if you
如果你想编译它，如果你
want to if you want to if you want to
想要如果想要的话
run it and have the modules properly
运行它并正确安装模块
resolved for you yes you need to require
为您解决，是的，您需要
it that's okay so the required is for
没关系，所以需要
static references it will give me a nice
静态引用会给我一个很好的
compiler I don't have to wait for
编译器，我不必等待
runtime but if it's by reflection I mean
运行时，但如果通过反思，我的意思是
I can't get away with compiling unless I
除非我不能放弃编译
use required I mean I can't correct okay
需要使用我的意思是我无法纠正
all right unless you want to write all
好吧，除非你想写全部
of your code reflectively just too
反射你的代码
painful I understand okay by the way we
痛苦的是，我了解我们的方式
just quit since you picked on the
自从你选择了之后就退出了
Jackson library in the indie advance
独立开发中的Jackson图书馆
talk which we repeat later on today we
我们今天稍后会重复的谈话
actually look at the for example the
实际看例如
Jackson data bind which is heavy use a
杰克逊数据绑定，这是一个大量使用
core reflection but it also has a number
核心反射，但它也有一个数字
of dependencies itself because Jackson
依赖本身，因为杰克逊
data bind it comes with those parts the
数据绑定是这些部分附带的
annotations are parts of Jackson core it
注释是Jackson核心的一部分
requires actually it requires XML it
需要它实际上需要XML它
requires sequel there's a bunch of
需要续集，有一堆
things that actually require so we
实际需要的东西，所以我们
actually use J tips to even look at its
实际上使用J技巧甚至看它
dependencies we will actually produce a
依赖，我们实际上会产生一个
a module info declaration just to show
一个模块信息声明只是为了显示
what it would actually look like so and
它实际上看起来像什么，
you'll actually get to see all of that
您实际上会看到所有这些
if anybody's watching live on the stream
如果有人在看直播
feel free to send questions in via
随时通过发送问题
Twitter we'll do our best to answer them
Twitter我们将尽力回答他们
there is something that I don't
有一些我不喜欢的东西
understand from the advanced understood
从高级中了解
that the model system is is agnostic to
该模型系统不可知
the class loaders right so if I have for
类加载器正确，所以如果我有
example two versions of Jackson each one
例如每个版本的Jackson的两个版本
of them is loaded with different class
他们中有不同的阶级
holders and for one of them it trick
持有人，其中之一就骗了
export something and for another it
出口东西，然后再出口
exports another thing then it seems like
出口另一件事然后看起来像
it needs to be aware of the fact that it
它需要意识到以下事实：
is okay so let me make sure I've got the
没关系，所以让我确保我已经
scenario right yet you have two versions
场景正确，但您有两个版本
of Jackson yeah they're both they're
杰克逊是的，他们俩都是
both they both have the same module name
它们都具有相同的模块名称
yeah okay so you could you could load
是的，好的，所以您可以加载
each one into a separate class loader
每个都放入一个单独的类加载器
and you can make each class loader be in
您可以将每个类加载器放入
its own layer this is what I was trying
它自己的层，这就是我正在尝试的
to explain in the Nettie scenario
在Nettie场景中进行解释
earlier has two different layers with
早期有两个不同的层
different applications running in the
在
same same fee and they're hosted by some
同样的费用，它们由一些托管
container app and they're using
容器应用，他们正在使用
different version exports right the mob
不同版本出口暴民
system it will be will implicitly be
系统将隐式地
aware of that because they're in
意识到这一点，因为他们在
different layers so the so that the
不同的层次，以便
constraint is within a let within a
约束在一个让内
layer you can only have one module of
一层只能有一个模块
any given name so even if the packages
任何给定的名称，即使包装
conflict that's okay
可以的冲突
that the unit the unit of export is
出口单位是
packaged if we made it if we made the
如果我们做到了就打包
unit of export be a single class we
出口单位为单一类
would all be very unhappy with
都会非常不满意
performance its it also just doesn't you
表演它也不是你
know in practical terms doesn't seem to
实际上知道似乎
be necessary most of the components
是大多数组件所必需的
we've looked at and we've looked at a
我们已经看过，我们已经看过
lot maven maintains in an internal clone
很多专家维护内部克隆
of maven central that we that we survey
我们调查的Maven Central的
to ask these kinds of questions you know
问这些你知道的问题
generally a package is meant to have an
通常，包装是指具有
API that's used by your a comfo
您的comfo使用的API
component will have it packages that are
组件将具有
meant to use by be used by other
打算被其他人使用
components and others that are internal
组件和其他内部组件
and it's it's fairly uncommon to find a
并且找到一个是相当不常见的
package that has both internal and
具有内部和
external stuff it does happen but yeah
确实发生了外部问题，但是
move move move move move the internal
移动内部内部移动
stuff to a different package that you
东西放到另一个包裹里
don't export yep one other point to make
不要出口是另一点
on that is there's there's no
在那边没有
requirement that the
要求
the classes in your module are version
您模块中的类是版本
53 or older you may actually have
您可能实际有53岁或以上
classes that works you compile for an
您可以编译的类
older version and there's nothing in the
较旧的版本，没有任何内容
class file that actually tell is that
实际告诉的类文件是
what module it's in so when you start
它在什么模块中，所以当您启动时
thinking through that you'll actually
想着，你实际上
realize that the the the unit of export
认识到出口的单位
being or the granularity of exporting
出口或出口的粒度
package kind of really does make sense
包装真的很有意义
in those scenarios
在那些情况下
anybody has maven questions Robert
任何人都对罗伯特有疑问
Salty's here
咸在这里
well he's your many years Stephen good
好吧，他是你多年的斯蒂芬·好
morning hello good morning oh you have a
早上好，早上好，哦，你有一个
list I have woken up yes I was thinking
清单我已经醒了，是的，我在想
about things overnight I've only got two
一夜之间我只有两个
things on the list so it's quite sure if
清单上的东西，所以很确定
we have module a module a that is
我们有一个模块a是
requiring module B hmm can module B see
要求模块B嗯，模块B可以看到吗
code in module a is that actually
模块a中的代码实际上是
prevented by the module system or just
被模块系统阻止或只是
because typically you can't compile
因为通常您无法编译
module B so so sometimes so if a
模块B，所以有时，如果a
requires B then B cannot require a sure
需要B然后B不能要求确定
but you could have code in B that uses
但是您可以在B中使用以下代码
reflection to read things in a ok
反思阅读确定
assuming the de exports the short and
假设德出口空头，
that's fine I understand that part but
很好，我了解那部分，但是
could be have been compiled in some
可能已经被编译成一些
other way the web I previously got a
其他方式，我以前得到的网络
reference to a class E oh sure yeah if
引用E类，哦，是的，如果
you have some if yeah if you have some
你有一些，如果有的话
broken your broken tool train or some
打破了破碎的工具列或某些
weird provenance of the classes and B
类和B的怪异出处
then you you could certainly have having
那么你当然可以拥有
a weird situation that you would expect
您期望的一种奇怪的情况
to work at runtime but it wouldn't okay
可以在运行时正常工作，但是不行
so would block it the Martin if you may
所以如果你愿意的话，会阻止它马丁
if you managed to create a a and B and
如果您成功创建了aa和B，
their module descriptors had each
他们的模块描述符都有
requiring the other which you know you
要求你认识你的另一个
could do at runtime the module system
可以在运行时完成模块系统
would refuse to load it would it would
会拒绝加载它会
stop and and tell you that you have a
停下来告诉你，你有一个
cycle in your module graph okay but the
可以在模块图中循环，但是
question why I had was if a requires B
问我为什么要a是否需要B
and B does not require a but B does
并且B不需要a但B却需要
contain some code that refers to a will
包含一些涉及遗嘱的代码
that work no you will get an illegal
那项工作不，你会得到非法的
access or okay remember accessibility is
访问或确定记住可访问性是
a two-way street yeah and in that
是一条双向路，在那
scenario where it requires B and then B
它需要B然后B的情况
somehow has been compiled in some funny
不知何故被编译成一些有趣的东西
way it's got a static reference to
静态引用的方式
something in a but it doesn't read it so
里面有东西，但看不懂
that so readability is part of the
因此，可读性是
access
访问
okay so in order for that access check
好的，为了进行访问检查
to work is is we would have to read a
工作是我们必须阅读一本
and a wouldn't need to export whatever
而且不需要出口任何东西
the the packages with that type to at
该类型的包装在
least be now it may be there at runtime
至少现在可以在运行时在那里
be uses the reflective API to read a and
被使用反射API读取a和
in that case that will work here but in
在这种情况下，它将在这里工作，但在
this in this mismatch between
这之间的不匹配
compile-time and run-time environments
编译时和运行时环境
then that that access check will
那么该访问检查将
actually fail okay now what if a is a
现在实际上失败了，如果a是一个
week module as opposed to a strong
周模块而不是强大
module does that change it no no that
模块会改变它吗
only changes what B can get out of our
只有改变B才能从我们身上得到
reflection it gives it more it does not
反思它给它更多它没有
change what B reads at the get-go yeah
改变B一开始就读的内容
I'll have to think about that because my
我必须考虑一下，因为我的
impression was the eye is affected
印象是眼睛受到影响
exporting all packages yes it is it is
导出所有软件包是的
but it's but it's not making the read a
但这不是在读
right we a week module is just one that
对，我们一个星期的模块只是一个
exports private every one of its
出口私人的每一个
packages so B would still need to read
包，所以B仍然需要阅读
it which
它哪个
just give me a second to
请给我一点
it's an intro
这是一个介绍
here we go
开始了
this is our two-way street
这是我们的两条街
in the indian trajectory have a couple
在印度的轨迹上有一对
of Statistics modules there's a there's
统计模块的存在
a stat score which has exports a bunch
统计得分，已导出一堆
of AP is for things like regression and
的AP用于诸如回归和
clustering and so on and then we have a
聚类等等，然后我们有一个
CLI which is a command line interface
CLI是命令行界面
that requires stat score so and so so
需要统计得分等等
CLS that's Eli requires stat score in
属于Eli的CLS需要统计得分
other words it actually will read it and
换句话说，它实际上会阅读它，
therefore that gives it access to the
因此，它可以访问
public types in the packages that are
包中的公共类型是
exported by bikes by stat score so this
按统计得分按自行车输出，因此
is this is a two-way street
这是两条路吗
now suppose that I'm sorry one other
现在假设我很抱歉
thing about the stat score is is in the
统计得分的事情是在
example is there's a bunch of internal
例如有很多内部
packages as well and no types in those
包以及其中没有类型
packages are accessible to anybody
包可供任何人访问
outside of stat score let us suppose
统计得分以外的地方让我们假设
that stats Eli did not read stat score
统计数据Eli没有读取统计数据分数
that would mean that nothing is
那意味着什么都没有
accessible to just to start score
刚开始就可以得分
sorry just know that nothing is
对不起，只知道什么都没有
accessible to stats Eli because it does
统计数据Eli可以访问，因为它确实
not read stat score so I think in your
看不到统计得分，所以我认为
scenario is is if I put a and B labels
场景是如果我放上A和B标签
to replace what I have here then I think
取代我在这里的东西，我想
you're saying that stat score is a week
您是说统计得分是一周
module stats Eli does not read it so
模块统计Eli并不这样阅读
therefore any the static references will
因此任何静态引用都会
actually fail at runtime because it
实际上在运行时失败，因为它
doesn't read it
不读
now I think I know you've put wood week
现在我想我知道你已经放木了
on either of these this axis will still
在这两个轴上，
fail because there's there's no
失败，因为那里没有
dependency declare it in your module
依赖关系在模块中声明
declaration therefore there's no
声明，因此没有
readability at one time what as Mark
一次可读性和Mark一样
said core reflection will work just fine
说核心反射会很好
since nobody else is diving into ask
因为没有其他人潜入询问
another question right a second I'll ask
我马上要问另一个问题
my second questions so we have automatic
我的第二个问题，所以我们有自动
modules and the name of the automatic
模块和自动名称
module is derived from the file name yes
模块是从文件名派生的
Bart's in standard maven approach the
巴特的标准行家方法
file name the maven file name does not
文件名maven文件名不
correspond to the name to which you
对应于您的名字
would normally wish to declare the
通常希望声明
module ie the reverse domain name list
模块，即反向域名列表
so guava would be typically should be
所以番石榴通常应该是
released as Condor Google guava if you
如果您以Condor Google番石榴发布
actually declared a module name
实际声明了模块名称
joda-time is actually the maiden name
joda-time实际上是娘家的名字
has a dash in it but you really wanted
有一个破折号，但你真的想要
to be all cocky adore time now it seems
现在似乎都是自大崇拜
to me that if you're an open source
对我来说，如果您是开源的
project that publishes dependency on an
发布依赖项的项目
automatic module which is derived from
派生自的自动模块
the short name that's given to the jar
罐子的简称
file when that module is actually
该模块实际存在时的文件
released in the future by its owner your
将来由其所有者发布
open source project will now no longer
开源项目现在将不再
be acceptable to the world so it seems
可以被世界接受
to me that it would be a very bad idea
对我来说，这将是一个非常糟糕的主意
for any open source project to publish a
让任何开源项目发布一个
project based on an automatic mortal eye
基于自动凡人之眼的项目
so there is several things here but upon
所以这里有几件事
which to comment one can turn that
对此发表评论可以使这一点
around and say that well if if if since
周围说好吧，如果，如果因为
guava today is guava - you know version
番石榴今天是番石榴-你知道版本
number jar as an automatic module its
数字罐作为自动模块
name will be simply guava one could say
名字可能就是番石榴
alternatively that the maintainer of
或者说，
guava if and when they turn that into a
番石榴，如果他们把它变成一个
proper explicit module if they care
适当的显式模块（如果他们愿意）
about their users they should call that
关于他们的用户，他们应该打电话给
module guava rather than kombu GLE dot
模块番石榴而不是kombu GLE点
collections that way whatever using
无论使用哪种方式收集
because it requires whoever gets there
因为它要求任何人到达那里
first to win and be able to do well
首先赢得并能够做好
effectively effectively they are
他们有效地
effectively they already all are are
实际上，他们已经都是
their first because you know guava -
他们的第一个，因为你知道番石榴-
version whatever it is jar is is what
版本无论罐子是什么
goes on the class path yeah but I mean
走上上课的路，是的，但是我的意思是
the module name is something you should
模块名称是您应该使用的名称
be picky
挑剔
dependently of that yeah well my name is
取决于那是的，我的名字是
I mean II think that it the specs are
我是说II认为规格是
defining that motor names are meant to
定义电动机名称旨在
be with the soleus so so so we so we
与比目鱼呆在一起所以所以我们所以我们
could we could just we could just take
我们可以，我们可以
out automatic modules I think what would
出自动模块，我想会
be nice it would be have to have
很好，那将不得不
something written up on recommendations
关于建议的东西
for module names module names are really
对于模块名称，模块名称实际上是
important they're going to be part of
重要的是，他们将成为
what you require and what you do and
您需要什么和做什么
what you depend on I think that our
你所依赖的我认为我们
position on this side of the table would
放在桌子这一侧的位置
be not to use the Google bla bla bla bla
请勿使用Google bla bla bla bla
as the name of your module we would
作为模块的名称，我们将
actually call that guava so it actually
真的叫那个番石榴，所以实际上
closer to the artifact name not the
更接近工件名称而不是
package name yeah and and this has
包名称是的，这有
actually been a gradual shift in our in
实际上是我们在逐步转变
our own view if you look if you look at
如果你看的话，我们自己的看法
for example the current state of the
例如当前的状态
module system which is a few months out
模块系统要几个月了
of date it recommends reverse DNS as
建议使用反向DNS作为日期
time has gone on as we and as we've got
随着时间的流逝，时间的流逝
more experience we've realized you know
更多的经验，我们已经意识到您知道
you know for one thing there's that
你知道一件事就是
there's this whole additional question
还有这整个问题
which you and others have raised of how
您和其他人提出了如何
do you distinguish a module name from a
您是否将模块名称与
package name in a module declaration it
包名称在模块中声明
it can it can look a bit it can be kind
它可以看起来有点好吗
of confusing to be reading a module
混淆阅读模块
declaration and see the module name is
声明，然后查看模块名称为
calm dog food bar and then it exports a
冷静的狗粮吧，然后出口
package called calm dog food bar and
包叫镇定狗粮吧
there's no visual distinction now
现在没有视觉上的区别
there's all syntax bike shed about well
所有语法自行车都很好
we could have a completely different
我们可以有一个完全不同的
syntax for module names and we've been
模块名称的语法，我们已经
we painted that bike shed a bunch of
我们把那辆自行车漆成一堆
different colors and nothing better than
不同的颜色，没有什么比这更好的了
dots have shown up so if you if you
点已经出现，所以如果你
accept that if you accept that it's
如果接受，那就接受
going to be dots then hat and not using
将是点然后是帽子而不是使用
reverse dns for module names becomes a
模块名称的反向dns变为
bit more attractive because then you can
更具吸引力，因为这样您就可以
just say well it that the module name is
只是说好模块名称是
foo because well after all this is
foo，因为毕竟这是
winding up and you know food - 1 2 3 jar
清盘，你知道食物-1 2 3罐
and the packet the package names still
和包的包名称仍然
you you use reverse DNS or a similar
您使用反向DNS或类似的域名
convention if nothing else to minimize
约定，如果没有其他要最小化的地方
conflicts in class loaders so I I mean I
类加载器发生冲突，所以II表示我
I understand the appeal of using reverse
我了解使用反向的吸引力
DNS for module names
DNS作为模块名称
I have to say it doesn't appeal to me
我不得不说这对我没有吸引力
not to usually this well you are
通常你不会这样
certainly free to use reverse DNS model
当然可以免费使用反向DNS模型
names for a model a lot more companies
为更多公司命名的模型
have internal projects which will have a
有内部项目将有一个
name and that name a sudden these future
名字和那个名字突然这些未来
clash with some big open source project
与一些大型开源项目发生冲突
because obviously the team there's no
因为很明显，团队没有
connection between the two yeah there's
两者之间的联系是的
a timeline issue and projects like
时间表问题和类似的项目
joda-time which have a - in the name or
joda-time的名称-
maven will obviously have - can't have a
专家显然会-无法拥有
- in the name it's well there's the
-以它的名义很好
automatic module naming our algorithm
自动模块命名我们的算法
that converts the - into attacks easy
将-轻松转换为攻击
that's certainly at the very least you
至少肯定是你
said he would need to write up a module
说他需要写一个模块
naming documentation about what your
命名有关您的内容的文档
name is strategy is I'm surprised that
名字是策略，我很惊讶
you're considering not reverse domain
您正在考虑不反向域名
name I'll leave it that you so surprised
我留下你的名字我很惊讶
noted well yeah maybe were to be honest
说得很好，也许是说实话
we're a little bit nervous about it -
我们对此有点紧张-
cuz I was going to suggest but maybe the
因为我打算建议，但也许
naming subsidy should look at what the
命名补贴应该看一下
route package is within the jar file so
路由包位于jar文件中，因此
determining about how people can
确定人们如何能够
interpreting that automatically and you
自动解释，你
had used confusing to a route package as
使用混淆路由包作为
the name yeah the the the beauty of the
是的，名字的美
current convention is it makes automatic
当前的惯例是它可以自动
modules pretty easy to reason about and
模块非常容易推理和
automatic modules are of significant
自动模块非常重要
benefit to the whole migration story
受益于整个移民故事
right if we if we didn't have automatic
对，如果我们没有自动的话
modules then we'd be forcing everybody
模块，那么我们将迫使所有人
into bottom-up migration and it'll and
进行自下而上的迁移，它将和
that would take 20 years to be adopted
要花20年才能被采纳
or having a text file that Maps module
或具有“地图”模块的文本文件
name to Java makes sure you can solve
Java的名称确保您可以解决
any problem with yet another level of
另一个层次的任何问题
indirection
间接的
questions anyway okay thank you
反正问题还好谢谢
I have an open-source project which uses
我有一个使用
tools good job I'm sorry yeah Jeff 220
工具不错，对不起杰夫220
yeah so two tools jars gone it's
是的，所以两个工具罐都消失了
actually been gone for a long time if
实际上已经消失了很长时间
you if you need to get to the compiler
如果您需要使用编译器
that then you should use the compiler
那你应该使用编译器
API which has actually been around for
实际上已经存在的API
multiple releases at this point we're
此时，我们发布了多个版本
using two is that what you were using
用两个就是你在用
tools about the board oh you're you're
关于董事会的工具哦，你就是
you're you're out you're you're using an
你在外面，你在用
internal API in tools about jar
关于jar的工具中的内部API
well tools are no longer exists that
好的工具已经不存在
class exists somewhere it is almost
类几乎存在于某个地方
certainly encapsulated if you want to go
当然要封装，如果你想去
you know play you know played by violate
你知道打法你知道打法
encapsulation and do reflection magic
封装并做反射魔术
you can you can still use it but it's a
您可以仍然可以使用它，但这是一个
completely unsupported API
完全不受支持的API
which API are you using actually hotspot
您实际使用的是哪个API
dynasty mxb nor their there are
王朝MXB也没有
different api's to dump threats the
不同的API转储威胁
latest in gdk9 which you might not want
您可能不想要的gdk9最新版本
to use yet is step walk step walker it's
要使用的是踏步机，它是
a new API allow you to walk the entire
新的API可让您遍历整个
stat and filter out its just returning
统计并过滤掉它刚刚返回
your stream of step frame so you could
您的步框流，因此您可以
flexibly filter anything and you allow
灵活地过滤任何东西，您允许
you to access the class object as well
您也可以访问类对象
so this is the latest one if you just
所以这是最新的
want to stack trace strings there our
想要在其中堆叠跟踪字符串
thread gets that trace gets that traces
线程获取该跟踪线程获取该跟踪
it has been there since JDK five I
自从JDK 5以来，它就一直存在
believe Locke yes yes well no sorry it
相信Locke是是很好不抱歉
it the Locke information if you depends
如果您依赖的话，它是洛克信息
what you're looking for is in javelin
您要寻找的是标枪
management which is it's a public API
管理是公共API
you don't need to use to start off but
您不需要使用开始但
it's not in the Java based that what I
我不是基于Java
mean is in Java dot management module
意思是在Java点管理模块中
but it's a public support API is Java SE
但这是Java SE的公共支持API
API
API
look at Java Lane management threat MX
再看Java Lane管理威胁MX
been there is a lock info returned to
是否有锁信息返回给
you so you can inspect who yeah the
您可以检查谁是
owner who locked who is holding the lock
谁锁谁拥有谁的锁
yeah it has been there since JDK 5 + j
是的，自JDK 5 + j起就一直在那里
TK 6 enhancing it yeah for Java you to
TK 6增强了对Java的支持
conquer locks that stack Walker API that
征服堆栈Walker API的锁
Mandy mentioned it's actually really
曼迪说这是真的
nice but to your point about whether
很好，但要指出的是
that class is still that intern class is
那个班还是那个实习班
still there yesterday yes it is there
昨天还在那里是的
you don't actually tools that jar may be
你实际上并没有用工具
gone but that class is actually still
没了，但是那堂课实际上还是
that type is actually still visible I
该类型实际上仍然可见
don't know how you're accessing it as a
不知道您是如何访问它的
class for name or you've got a static
名称类，或者您有一个静态名称
reference but you will get an illegal
参考，但您将获得非法
access error legal access exception if
访问错误合法访问异常，如果
you use it yes senator what you internal
你用它是参议员你内部
API you are using so I will at it in the
您正在使用的API，因此我会在
Jade apps wiki and tell you the
Jade应用程式Wiki，并告诉您
replacement yeah my questions this app
替换是的，我对这个应用程序有疑问
that it's not working under JDK 9 I just
它在JDK 9下不起作用，我只是
figured out why
弄清楚为什么
so it's runs under security manager
因此它在安全管理器下运行
because it's run by students and and you
因为它是由学生和你经营的
don't trust your student no I don't know
不信任你的学生，不，我不知道
yeah every once in a while I get a
是的，每隔一段时间我会得到一个
report from someone else who managed to
向其他设法举报的人举报
crack something and so it it compiles
破解一些东西，然后编译
Java code and the way it's done right
Java代码及其正确完成方式
now is that tools jar is given all
现在是工具罐被赋予了所有
permission in the policy file now with
现在在策略文件中具有权限
tools touch never having gone away who
工具触摸永远不会消失谁
do I give all permission JDK compiler so
我授予所有权限JDK编译器
there's so which a decaying age and
有这样一个衰落的年龄，
older my guess is is that you would have
我的猜测是年纪大了
granted and you would have given a a
当然，你会给一个
code base that is the file path to to
代码库，即到的文件路径
write the equivalent with JDK 9 and
用JDK 9和
modules is you grant the permission to
模块是您授予的权限
Jay arty :
杰伊·阿蒂（Jay arty）：
slash and then the module name in this
斜杠，然后是模块名
case probably it's JDK compiler is the
情况可能是JDK编译器
name of the module
模块名称
it's actually really nice it's really
真的很好，真的
really nice because you can do it on per
真的很好，因为您可以按
module basis all the details of this are
模块基础的所有详细信息是
written up in chapter 20 okay and if you
写在第20章好吧，如果你
look at the JDK 9 download look at the
看看JDK 9下载看看
comp security policy file is moved to
comp安全策略文件已移至
the configuration directory look at that
配置目录看看
existing file you will see their
现有文件，您将看到他们的
examples because we are granting a
例子，因为我们授予
number of JDK modules with fine-grained
细粒度的JDK模块数量
permissions already
已有权限
in little one man is exactly right there
只有一个人正好在那儿
are examples in the indicator case
是指标案例的例子
default policy where were granting
授予默认策略
permissions to specific modules yeah
特定模块的权限是的
okay syntax is really really easy to
好的语法真的很容易
work
工作
now Twitter questions too early we had
现在Twitter问题我们还为时过早
quite a few last year that was it this
去年很多就是这个
time
时间
everybody wake up there
大家在那里醒来
if you have a web application closer to
如果您的Web应用程序更接近
the mic please if you have web
麦克风，如果您有网络请
application how would the automatic
应用程序将如何自动
modules work and is there a standard
模块工作，是否有标准
about how I think that's a question
关于我如何认为这是一个问题
probably for the Java EE 9 expert group
可能是针对Java EE 9专家组的
so that we can actually start migrating
这样我们才能真正开始迁移
when server 9 comes out so we can build
当服务器9出现时，我们可以构建
modules still just right so so so so the
模块仍然是正确的，所以这样，所以
hope the hope and expectation is that
希望希望和期望是
Java EE 9 will leverage this module
Java EE 9将利用此模块
system exactly how it does so is not for
系统到底是怎么做的，不是为了
any of us here you're here to say
我们任何一个人在这里都在说
obviously we you know we've been working
显然，您知道我们一直在努力
with a number of the you know experts
与许多您认识的专家
and spec leads to get feedback but I you
和规格导致获得反馈，但我你
know I I have no idea what a modular
知道我不知道什么是模块化
year will look like you know III can
一年，就像你知道的
certainly you know I would if I had to
当然，您知道如果需要的话我会的
guess I would hope among a modular wor a
猜想我希望在模块化工作中
modular year would look a lot like it
模块化年份看起来很像
does today except that the jar files
今天除了罐子文件
would be modular jars and the the e op
将是模块化的罐子和e op
server machinery that loads them would
加载它们的服务器机器会
would use the the modulus as the system
将使用模数作为系统
resolver to build a module graph and a
解析器构建模块图和
layer and just have all that work so you
层，并完成所有工作，所以您
know the easy easy answer is well sure
知道简单容易的答案很确定
go ahead and make modules but for a
继续制作模块，但要
while yet when when those are loaded
当这些被加载时
into into an EE container or a servlet
放入EE容器或servlet
container they're just gonna be on the
容器，他们只是要放在
class path like they thought they've
像他们认为的那样上课的路
always been but if you use those same
一直以来，但如果您使用相同的
modules in other contexts then they can
在其他情况下的模块，那么他们可以
actually be used as modules make sense
实际上用作模块有意义
yeah
是的
if in my application I have very small
如果在我的应用程序中我很小
container and that's creates two layers
容器，这将创建两层
that both load up lots of different
两者都加载了很多不同的东西
classifiers let's do some Java files
分类器让我们做一些Java文件
presumably those two layers and those
大概是这两层
classifiers are completely independent
分类器是完全独立的
one other that there is no sharing
彼此之间没有共享
whatsoever between them there is no
他们之间没有任何关系
sharing between them that is directly
他们之间直接共享
enabled by the module system but
由模块系统启用但
remember there's always reflection so at
记住总是有反思，所以在
at runtime code yeah no no no it's not
在运行时代码是，不，不，不是
true that all bets are off
确实所有赌注都没有
but at runtime code in a module in the
但是在运行时，
first layer could add add a runtime
第一层可以添加添加运行时
reads edge from that module to a module
从该模块读取边缘到模块
in the other layer and if that module
在另一层，如果该模块
exports stuff then the first module will
出口的东西，那么第一个模块将
be able to access it how would I even
能够访问它，我什至会
know about the other bias if it leaks
了解其他偏差是否泄漏
through an API or or you you can you can
通过API或您可以
you can if it's somehow somehow gets old
您可以通过某种方式变老
of the hold of the layer it's it's
层的保持力是
certainly you know it's possible yeah I
当然，您知道这是可能的，我
guess I was trying to work out so what's
猜猜我在努力锻炼，所以
the what's the degree of isolation
什么是隔离度
between these two layers because
在这两层之间，因为
obviously there's isolation which is
显然有隔离是
good in that you can't sort the other
优点在于您无法将其他排序
thing I mess it up but there's also I
我把它弄乱了，但还有我
imagine it's bad as in you end up with
想象这很糟糕，因为你最终会
two copies of audio day tree and static
音频日树和静态的两个副本
sorts right so so isolation is a
排序正确，所以隔离是
different thing than encapsulation right
与封装权不同
we're trying to provide strong
我们正在努力提供强大的
encapsulation that's that's that's
那就是那的封装
fairly hard although not although not
相当困难，尽管不是
impossible to break we are not trying to
不可能打破，我们不是要
provide isolation I think it says some
提供隔离我认为它说一些
some sort of you know hard boundary
你们知道某种硬边界
that's him that's impenetrable between
那是他之间不可穿透的
different layers if you need that kind
如果需要的话，可以分为不同的层
of hard boundary than operating system
硬边界比操作系统
processes or your friend
流程或您的朋友
work on a very heavily configuration
在非常繁重的配置上工作
driven project where much of our code
驱动的项目，其中很多代码
knows not about other resources that
不知道其他资源
it's going to need to load so we have
它需要加载，所以我们有
many configuration files that are loaded
许多已加载的配置文件
by their location on the class path
根据他们在课程路径上的位置
which live in jars that are much much
放在很多的罐子里
higher than the classes that need to see
高于需要看的课程
them
他们
I'm sorry higher along what dimension so
对不起，更高的尺寸
if we were to draw a graph we have
如果我们要画一个图
configuration level jars which depend on
配置级别的jar取决于
code level jars okay but they all wind
代码级的罐子可以，但是它们都缠绕
up on the linear class power they do
依靠他们做的线性类能力
okay will our code that's in the lower
好的，我们的代码在下面
level modules be able to see the
级别的模块能够看到
resources that are in the higher level
较高级别的资源
module so the configuration modules only
模块，因此仅配置模块
contain resource files yes it to pay it
包含资源文件是的，要付钱
depends on how it depends on how things
取决于它如何取决于事物
are named so in in in the in the current
被命名为
system resources are encapsulated but
系统资源已封装但
only when they're effective package name
仅当它们是有效的包装名称时
is actually alleged legitimate Java
实际上是合法的Java
package name so if you're putting if
包裹名称，如果你放
you're part of putting configuration
您是配置的一部分
files in you know meta - infor you know
您知道的文件meta-您知道的信息
so some long string that that that can't
如此长的字符串
be converted into a Java package name
转换为Java包名称
then that will always be exported and if
那么它将始终被导出，如果
you you have code in the same class
你在同一个类中有代码
loader org or code that could that's in
加载器组织或可能在其中的代码
a module that reads that module you'll
读取该模块的模块
you'll be able to load the resource no
您将能够加载资源
problem
问题
can you explain one more times the
你能再解释一次吗
difference between the JDK nine regular
JDK九个常规之间的区别
early-access release and the one with
抢先体验版和
jigsaw the one with jigsaw is bleeding
拼图的人正在流血
edge so what the way the the the JDK 9
边缘那么JDK 9的方式如何
one is is is somewhat less bleeding edge
一种是出血边缘稍少
what's bleeding well you know when it
你知道什么时候在流血
hurts what difference is might I expect
伤害了我可能期望的区别
well it it varies over time right they
好吧，随着时间的流逝，他们会改变
we as we as we evolved the the model
我们随着我们发展模型
system all the stuff around it in
将周围的所有东西都放入
response to feedback and further
对反馈的回应和进一步
thinking we do that fairly quickly in
认为我们在
the jigsaw forest in open JDK we do it
在开放式JDK中进行拼图森林操作
with with less rigorous code review and
与较少严格的代码审查和
less QA so that you know there's
减少质量检查，以便您知道
certainly some testing on it but
当然可以进行一些测试，但是
basically what you're seeing in the
基本上，您在
jigsaw ei is our continuous integration
拼图EI是我们不断的融合
build of the very latest jigsaw bits
最新拼图的构建
what you see in the JDK 9 EA is a a more
您在JDK 9 EA中看到的更多
carefully evolved code base where
精心开发的代码库
everything is code reviewed there has
一切都有代码审查那里
been more testing on it you know
对此进行了更多测试
certainly not complete but you more it
当然还不完整，但是你更多
more than you'll find on jigsaw and it
超过您在拼图上能找到的
could be you know it could be at times
可能是您知道有时可能
quite a bit behind what's in the jigsaw
拼图中有很多东西
EA and that's that's the case right now
EA，现在就是这种情况
often they're in sync and there been a
通常他们是同步的，并且有一个
couple of times during nine where we've
我们在九点的几次
stopped publishing the jigsaw EA is
停止发布拼图EA
because we've been doing all of our work
因为我们一直在做所有的工作
in JDK 9 and we'll probably get to
在JDK 9中，我们可能会
another phase like that this fall
今年秋天的另一个阶段
difference between them is a Corbett
他们之间的区别是Corbett
it's completely broken bills nobody has
这是完全破账单的人都没有
noticed we will fix it of course before
注意到我们当然会修复它
it goes into JDK 9 but it's exactly as
它进入JDK 9，但与
Mark said is this anything proposals
马克说这是什么建议
that mark is put out there we tried to
该标记被放在那里，我们试图
keep the implementation in sync with
与实施保持同步
that so many of the changes that are in
这么多的变化
the jukes EA bails our prototype quality
jukes EA称赞我们的原型质量
and refine things we tweak models for
并优化我们调整模型的内容
example are not in the JDK 9 EA but they
示例不在JDK 9 EA中，但它们
are in the jigsaw one
在拼图中
don't be shy nobody else is asking
不要害羞，没人问
questions right so that is a requirement
提出正确的问题，所以这是一个要求
as as yet unfulfilled but we realize
尚未实现，但我们意识到
there that there is is a need to be able
那里需要有能力
to scan modules for for classes that
扫描模块中的类
have certain annotations and so forth we
有某些注释，等等
have an idea of how to do that
知道如何做
it's not particularly hard we just
我们只是没有特别困难
haven't gotten to it yet but basically
尚未完成，但基本上
you know imagine a way to to introspect
你知道想像一种自省的方法
on a module and ask it you know what
在一个模块上，问你知道什么
what annotations are present and what
存在哪些注释以及什么
and which classes have them and then you
哪个班有他们，然后你
yeah well or even even the non exported
是的，甚至没有出口
ones because we know lots of CDI
因为我们知道很多CDI
frameworks operate on annotations that
框架在注释上运行
are on you know completely private
在你知道完全私人的
elements so that has to work too and
元素，所以也必须工作，
it's primarily a performance thing
这主要是性能的东西
anything that work any you're scanning
您正在扫描的任何有效工具
of classes on the class spot today
今天的上课地点
that'll all just work exactly as before
一切都会像以前一样工作
Robert let's try a hard one okay so this
罗伯特让我们努力一点，所以这
is probably a question about Java
可能是关于Java的问题
so suppose we are all convinced that
所以假设我们都相信
multipath is the way to go and we want
多路径是我们要走的路
to get rid of the classpath because
摆脱类路径，因为
right now we have during the compile
现在我们在编译期间
phase we can use multipath during just
阶段，我们可以在
compile we have to use right now both
编译我们现在都必须使用
class path and module path because of
类路径和模块路径，因为
the package collision you cannot add a
包冲突，您无法添加
module info inside the source main test
源主测试中的模块信息
directory and then we have the third
目录，然后我们有第三个
point where we need a multi-part and
点，我们需要一个多部分
that's during the running of the J unit
这是在J单元运行期间
tests and then we right now I have to
测试，然后我们现在我必须
fetch it and that's again when we have
拿来，那又是当我们有
to use the class path is there somewhere
使用类路径在某处
in the future probably a way to get rid
将来可能会摆脱
of the class path or else will there
上课的路径，否则会在那里
always be the class path will be with us
永远成为我们的课堂之路
until the heat death of the universe i I
直到宇宙的热死我我
just don't I don't see it ever going
只是不，我从没看到过
away i I would like to think there will
走了，我想在那里
be a day where it's used
成为使用的一天
you know rarely or only in situations
你很少或仅在某些情况下知道
like this where you have a good reason
像这样你有充分的理由
for it and the standard practice is to
为此，标准做法是
ship models and put them on the model
运送模型并将其放在模型上
path but yeah I do not think the class
路径，但是，我不认为这堂课
path will ever disappear
道路将永远消失
I I do hope I do hope that future
我确实希望我希望未来
platforms learn from the mistake of the
平台从错误中吸取教训
classpath and don't repeat it but you
类路径，不要重复，但是你
know here we are
知道我们在这里
no one else is asking and I'm trying to
没有人在问，我正在努力
debug my thing here please exception
在这里调试我的东西，请例外
somewhere in comm dots under tools some
在工具下一些通讯点中的某处
class that I've never heard of how do I
我从未听说过的课程
find out which module engine it should
找出应该使用哪个模块引擎
be in the stack trace
在堆栈跟踪中
so we've enhanced stack traces to
所以我们增强了堆栈跟踪
include module names and and if
包括模块名称以及if
appropriate even the names of class
甚至适合班级名称
loaders did you know class loaders can
装载机您知道类装载机可以
have names now this is I guess is a
现在有名字，我想这是一个
security manager access control
安全管理器访问控制
exception which doesn't have the module
没有模块的异常
name in it yet all right so we have in
在其中命名，还好吧，所以我们在
terms of improving hers and exceptions I
改善她的条件和例外
guess we can focus on more things like
猜想我们可以专注于更多的事情，例如
an illegal access xxx class cast
非法访问xxx类演员表
exception another sort of but we should
例外另一种，但我们应该
fix this one we should fix this back but
解决这个问题，我们应该解决这个问题，但是
if you so Java Java compiler is actually
如果您愿意，那么Java Java编译器实际上是
a standard module it exports the the
一个标准模块，它导出
standard Java X tools and Lulu but it
标准的Java X工具和Lulu，但是
doesn't contain a compiler which were
不包含编译器
confusing but oh it works very good so
令人困惑，但是哦，效果很好
many other bugs we can fix for any but
我们可以修复的其他许多错误
so well when you title this session mark
命名此会话标记时效果很好
hack session yeah okay we did some
hack session是的，好的，我们做了一些
hacking excellent well it is sure how
黑客出色，可以肯定
many people have have a have a jigsaw a
很多人有一个拼图
build on their laptops okay close the
建立在他们的笔记本电脑上，好关闭
rest of you can go can go melt the why
其余的你可以去融化为什么
fine get it now
好吧，现在就得到
yeah the Wi-Fi is is not bad this year
是的，今年的Wi-Fi不错
yeah the mornings pretty good I'm
是的，早上好，我是
curious actually how many people have
很好奇实际上有多少人
actually tried out j-league do some
实际尝试过J联赛做一些
runtimes jail in jail incur one person
监狱中的运行时监狱招致一个人
okay they work they work good
好吧，他们工作，他们工作得很好
will there be any kind of JVM options
是否会有任何类型的JVM选项
that would allow you to continue during
那将允许您在
a reflection inside the contacts and
触点内部的反射和
some packages there are out there
有一些包裹在那里
already are all right so there are
已经没事了，所以有
command-line options you can read about
您可以阅读的命令行选项
them in JEP 261 that allow you to break
他们在JEP 261中允许您突破
encapsulation good luck thank you rely
封装好运，谢谢依靠
on an internal API and report a bug
在内部API上并报告错误
against it it will be closed will not
反对它将被关闭不会
fix there's also some examples in the
修复里面还有一些例子
prepare for JDK 9 talk that we did on
为我们所做的JDK 9演讲做准备
Monday and ok great
星期一，还可以
and then on the topic of having
然后关于
dedicated on your laptop would it be
专门在笔记本电脑上
possible maybe for you to communicate
可能让你交流
with Symantec and have them execute it
与Symantec并让他们执行
from their antivirus reputation
从他们的防病毒声誉
something something I have tried to
我尝试过的东西
install it and it just disappears over
安装它，它消失了
and over so I can't use it on my
而且结束，所以我不能在我的身上使用它
corporate laptop um III have a Linux
公司笔记本电脑um III具有Linux
image on a flash drive if you want to
如果要在闪存驱动器上保存图像
borrow it
借它
sorry dad I don't even know if we do
抱歉，爸爸，我什至不知道我们是否愿意
communicate with Symantec regularly but
定期与Symantec通信，但
yeah I suppose we could look into it
是的，我想我们可以调查一下
I'll I'll ask one of our product
我要问我们的一种产品
managers if we have a channel there but
经理，如果我们在那里有渠道，但是
isn't there there's no way to adjust the
没有没有办法调整
antivirus thing yourself you're in a
您自己正在使用的防病毒软件
lockdown environment yeah I'm sorry I'm
锁定环境是的，对不起，我
so sorry
非常抱歉
Stephen is gonna ask the same question
斯蒂芬要问同样的问题
about McAfee hoping for a different
关于McAfee希望有所作为
answer I'm just going to note the Avast
我只是要记下Avast
security rejected the java and javac
安全拒绝了Java和Javac
executables when I tried to run them
当我尝试运行可执行文件时
when I donate the thing so this virus
当我捐赠东西时，这种病毒
check a thing it is common with early
早点检查这很常见
access products fortunately with Avast
幸运的是，可以使用Avast访问产品
you just uploaded the jar back to them
您刚刚将罐子上传回他们
and 19 minutes later they said yes it's
19分钟后，他们说是的
safe so ok it wasn't the end of all yeah
很安全，这还不是全部
that was a question sort of curiosity is
出于好奇，这是一个问题
is is that for every single build it was
是每一个构建
only what I tried I downloaded the early
只有我尝试过的，我下载了早期的
access build and it didn't object I
访问构建，它没有反对我
downloaded the jigsaw early access build
下载了拼图的抢先体验版
and it did oh yeah must it must be nicer
哦，是的，一定一定更好
who knows why that rip there things are
谁知道为什么那东西撕裂
but yeah yeah thought Java
但是，是的，以为Java
although Java was a virus and put it in
尽管Java是一种病毒，并将其放入
the chest Thanks I'll ask I'll ask our
胸部谢谢，我会问我会问我们
product management team if they have a
产品管理团队（如果有）
channel too
频道也
yeah my question was could you just go
是的，我的问题是你可以去吗
through j-mods verses jars I think
通过j-mods经文罐子
you're allowed to put J mods on the
您可以将J mods放在
module path why would you you just go
模块路径为什么你要走
through that so J mods
通过这样的J mods
n jars so jar files are what are what
n个jar，所以jar文件是什么
every developer and every build tool
每个开发人员和每个构建工具
already understands so it's a great
已经了解了，所以很棒
trick of modular jars is they're just
模块化罐子的窍门是它们只是
jar files that have this little extra
具有这些额外功能的jar文件
file in them and if you compile things
归档在其中，如果您编译的东西
correctly you could even use that to our
正确的，您甚至可以将其用于我们的
file in the class path and eight or
文件放在类路径中，然后输入8或
earlier J mods are or are a different
早期的J mod是不同的
format which we created because for the
我们创建的格式，因为
JDK itself we need we need an artifact
JDK本身，我们需要一个工件
type that can contain not just class
不仅可以包含类的类型
files but configuration files and native
文件，但配置文件和本机文件
libraries and launchers and license
库，启动器和许可证
files and man pages all this other sort
文件和手册页
of stuff and there's no there's no
的东西，没有没有
natural way to fit that into a jar that
将其放入罐子的自然方式
wouldn't be very confusing
不会很混乱
so j-mods at present they are there are
所以目前有j-mods
they are just zip files
它们只是zip文件
mandis working on on cleaning them up
Mandis正在努力清理它们
and and eventually will actually put a
并且最终将实际放一个
put a magic number at the front so that
在前面放一个魔术数字，以便
it's possible to distinguish them from
有可能将它们与
other other things that are actually a
其他实际上是
zip files going forward we might we
未来的zip文件，我们可能会
might change that format it's the the J
可能会更改该格式，这是J
mod format I think will will will not be
我认为不会的mod格式
part of the Java SE 9 spec but it will
Java SE 9规范的一部分，但它将
be documented you know it's certainly
被记录下来，你知道这肯定是
thought of people we want to use it that
想到我们要使用它的人
that'll be totally fine there's there's
那会没事的
a supported tool called J mod for
一个受支持的工具，称为J mod
creating and manipulating J mod files
创建和处理J mod文件
it's what we used to make all the j-mods
这就是我们用来制作所有j-mod的东西
the chip with the jdk at present J mods
目前J mods带有jdk的芯片
are only you can put them on the module
只是你可以把它们放在模块上
path but only a link time or yeah and
路径，但只有链接时间或
compile time they're there they're not
编译时间他们在那里，他们不在
they're not useful for runtime so if
它们对运行时没有用，所以如果
you're gonna play if you're gonna play
你会玩，如果你会玩
the linking game then then they're handy
链接游戏，那么他们就很方便
but if your ship if you want to ship
但是如果您要运送的话
things that can just go on the mod
可以在mod上进行的事情
module path at runtime then they're not
运行时的模块路径，则它们不是
what you want well they will they sip be
你想要什么，他们会they饮
supported at runtime in some future
将来会在运行时支持
release possibly but bullet bullet we'll
可能发布，但子弹我们会
see how it goes so I guess if we were to
看看进展如何，所以我想我们是否要
sort of summarize J mods as being then
总结当时的J mod
mostly for Oracle's internal purposes
主要用于Oracle的内部目的
would that be a terrible summary of them
那会是他们的糟糕总结吗
I
一世
we shouldn't be worried about well
我们不应该担心
though that III would quibble without
虽然那个三世会在没有
summary on two counts what one is it is
总结两点是什么
it's not Oracle internal write this is
不是Oracle内部写的，这是
open JDK I would expect any open JDK
打开JDK我希望有任何打开的JDK
derived distribution you know to support
您知道要支持的派生分布
j-mods unless they rip it out which
j-mods，除非他们将其淘汰
would be a dumb move III do think yeah
会是愚蠢的举动吗？
it's roughly correct that in in nine J
在九个J中大体上是正确的
mods are for the modules that comprised
mods用于包含的模块
the JDK I I won't be surprised to see
JDK II不会感到惊讶
some number of other J mod show up in
其他一些J mod出现在
particular for libraries that include a
特别是对于包含
bunch of native code
一堆本机代码
there will be a convenient way to ship
会有一种便捷的运送方式
but I you know certainly that I none of
但我当然知道我没有
us have any expect expectation the
我们有任何期望的期望
j-mods will replace jars at least not in
j-mods至少不会替换jar
the next couple years
接下来的几年
no please please come to the mic we it's
不，请进入我们的麦克风
actually hard for us to hear you if
如果我们真的很难听到你
you're standing no please the mics right
你站着不讨好麦克风
there yesterday could you please give us
昨天有你能给我们吗
the link because I couldn't find a
链接，因为我找不到
decision right so yeah so it's the
正确的决定，是的，这是
slides for all of the jigsaw sessions I
我所有的拼图游戏的幻灯片
will create a page linked to from the
将创建一个链接到的页面
jigsaw page probably later today with
拼图页面可能今天晚些时候与
all the PDFs and links to the video
所有PDF和视频链接
streams and all about if you if you I'll
流和所有有关您的信息，如果您愿意
tweet that out if nothing else you can
如果没有其他办法可以发推
find it there or just go to the jigsaw
在那找到它或只是去拼图
page in a couple of days you'll find it
几天之内就会找到它
another question we we work in two JVMs
我们在两个JVM中工作的另一个问题
so we start our IDE then called another
所以我们启动我们的IDE然后调用另一个
JVM for the user code to where well the
JVM将用户代码放到哪里
changes in JDK 9 affected in any way the
JDK 9中的更改以任何方式受到影响
tcp/ip conversation between the two JVMs
两个JVM之间的tcp / ip对话
or no ok thank you for watching
还是不好，谢谢收看
our multi release jars in scope for this
我们的多释放罐在此范围内
chat multi release jars are and they are
聊天多释放罐是，他们是
in JDK nine
在JDK九
yeah but are you taking questions oh
是的，但是你要提问哦
it's oh sure we can try and yeah and and
哦，可以确定，我们可以尝试
by the way they're really hairy edge
顺便说一句，他们真的是毛茸茸的边缘
cases between multi release jars and
多释放罐和
modular jars that we're still trying to
我们仍在尝试的模块化罐子
work out well I mean I really appreciate
锻炼得很好我的意思是我真的很感激
you guys doing multi police jars because
你们在做多警察罐，因为
well have a happy customer we've
我们有一个满意的客户
actually been we actually been wondering
实际上我们一直在想
is anybody gonna use these I'm up well I
有人会用这些吗？我很好
talked about them into prepare for JDK 9
谈论他们为JDK 9做准备
talked yesterday and repeating there's a
昨天谈话，并重复有一个
lot of questions ok so I've got a
好很多的问题，所以我有一个
library with an installed base that's
具有已安装基础的库
you know still on 5:00 and looking to
你知道还在5:00并期待
6:00 and so I'm wrapping you know a
6:00，所以我给你包了一个
parser event stream and I want it to be
解析器事件流，我希望它成为
auto closable when the underlying thing
当基础事物自动关闭
that I'm wrapping is auto close but I
我包装的是自动关闭的，但是我
wanted to reclosable and so auto
想重新封闭，所以自动
closable isn't available on five
不可关闭的五个
produces back in in seven years
在七年内生产回来
yeah so I do horrible things for five
是的，所以我做了五个可怕的事情
and six with reflection and so I'm
和六个反射，所以我
looking forward to that
期待着
and so my question is do you recommend
所以我的问题是你建议
building everything online with the
使用
release flag or what kind of machinery
释放标志或什么样的机械
around there is if I have to put our
周围是否有我必须把我们的
releases for I believe I have to put our
发布，因为我相信我必须把我们的
releases four five six seven eight and
发行四五六七七八和
nine book is putting out a five
九本书正在推出一个五
alright are you trying to create one
好吧，您是否要尝试创建一个
artifact that works on 5 6 7 8 &amp; 9
适用于5 6 7 8＆9的工件
yes and so what I think I can do is I
是的，所以我想我能做的是
think I can put out compile down to
想我可以把编译下来
source 5 and then I think I can 4 7 8 9
源5，然后我认为我可以4 7 8 9
I think I have to put out individuals or
我想我必须把个人或
I can put out one that so so - we 3 I'm
我可以这样说-我们3
sorry - 3 and my yeah and and and and -
抱歉-3和我是，还有and和-
3 week
3周
so hey we have no plans to back port
所以嘿，我们没有退港的计划
multi release jars t29 have in 6a not
多释放罐t29在6a中没有
not even to 8 ok so multi release jars
连8点都没有，所以多罐
are useful for dealing with differences
对处理差异很有用
from 8 to 9 and then later on 9 to 10
从8到9，然后在9到10
and so forth so we're we don't have
等等，所以我们没有
plans to back port them to 8 7 so
计划将其移植回8 7
they'll solve similar problems in the
他们会解决类似的问题
future but yeah sorry
未来，但是对不起
getting two really minor questions so
得到两个非常小的问题，所以
now with these policy files then I'm
现在有了这些策略文件，然后
gonna have to have two sets of policy
必须有两套政策
files because the jrt syntax is not
文件，因为jrt语法不是
accepted by jdk age that's true I have
我被jdk年龄接受了
argued in the past that it should be
过去认为应该
fatal but I'm pretty sure it's not and
致命的，但我敢肯定不是
so like I have things like j-unit in in
所以就像我在里面有j-unit之类的东西
my build because this tool runs j-unit
我的构建，因为此工具运行j-unit
on student code and so should I now go
在学生代码上，所以我现在应该去
back and make that into a module just
返回并将其放入模块中
wait for them to do it so just ignore it
等待他们去做，所以就忽略它
and just leave it as as an automatic
并把它作为自动
module what do people do I mean I could
模块人是什么意思
go in there and put in a module
进入那里并放入一个模块
declaration I didn't have it right and
声明我没有正确的选择
wrongly depend on hamcrest and all that
错误地依赖hamcrest等
but I wrote well I I assume you don't
但是我写得很好，我以为你不
really want to go in and change someone
真的很想进去改变一个人
else's jar file not particularly
其他的jar文件不是特别
that's sort of what what's a good
有点什么好
practice the good practice on until the
练习良好的做法，直到
maintainer zuv je-yoon is release a
维护者zuv je-yoon发布了
version of Jane it as a module then in
Jane的版本作为模块，然后在
the interim you can you can actually
你可以临时过渡
push a unit and hamcrest on the module
将单元推入模块
path as automatic module so we've
路径作为自动模块，所以我们已经
actually tried this out and it works
实际尝试了一下，它有效
pretty well ok I will try that
很好，我会尝试的
Thanks
谢谢
mr. Kolb or anybody else would have
先生。科尔布或其他任何人都会有
given you or got this maven central
给你或得到这个行家中央
thing you can actually go and figure out
你实际上可以去弄清楚的东西
lots of stuff about maven central jar
关于Maven中央罐的很多东西
files do you have a figure for what
文件你有什么数字
percentage of jar files on maven central
Maven Central上jar文件的百分比
for sensitive products projects have
对于敏感产品项目有
package name clashes between them
包名之间相互冲突
I know Commons beans utils the version
我知道Commons Bean utils的版本
before the latest version contained a
在最新版本包含
package from Commons collections yes I
来自Commons Collections的包装是
talked about that example and you say
谈到那个例子，你说
you know obviously this thing has
你知道这件事显然有
happened and that still happens I just
发生了，那仍然发生，我只是
wondered if you've done any analysis or
想知道您是否进行了任何分析或
to figure out how big a problem it was
找出问题有多严重
we done package conflict analyses I
我们完成了包裹冲突分析
didn't do it formally but the conflict
没有正式做，但是冲突
of package the volume i I did try many
我尝试过的包装数量
years ago but the volume is pretty high
年前但数量很大
because I have so many number of
因为我有很多
artifacts and there are some old
文物，还有一些旧的
versions as well so it is pretty high
版本也很高
but but not if you are asking about s
但不是，如果您要询问s
yeah API I don't have the number we have
是的，我没有我们的电话号码
to by now yeah yeah and it's and it's
到现在，是的，是的，是的
hard because if you if you what you know
很难，因为如果你知道的话
if you if you explore maven central you
如果您探索Maven Central，
can find you know there probably you can
可以找到你知道的地方
probably find hibernate under six
可能会在六岁以下找到冬眠
different group IDs which is extremely
不同的组ID，这非常
confusing because anybody can you know
令人困惑，因为任何人你都可以知道
upload it under some other group ID it's
将其上传到其他组ID下
our own pack version of it or whatever
我们自己的包装版本或其他
and so doing you know knowing what's
所以你知道什么吗
authoritative so that you could actually
权威，以便您实际上
do a package conflict analysis is pretty
做一个包冲突分析很漂亮
tough
强硬
I think it would be very useful if we
我认为如果我们
can find out what a really active
可以找出什么是真正活跃的
artifacts being used by projects and
项目使用的工件和
then from there those statistics are
然后从那里统计
more um yeah representative anything
更多，嗯，代表任何东西
yeah
是的
in the module info file be compiled
在模块信息文件中进行编译
separately yes a module info file can be
分别是，模块信息文件可以是
compiled separately so modules from JDK
单独编译，因此来自JDK的模块
I can strip out the module info and
我可以剥离模块信息并
insert my own modeling for there so that
在那儿插入我自己的模型，以便
I get wider access you you could do that
我得到了更广泛的访问，您可以这样做
you'd have to rerun the linker put yes
你必须重新运行链接器
you could if you really want to do that
如果您真的想这样做，可以
you could do that you cannot innovate
你可以做到你无法创新
the SEC accessible to true on reflection
反思后证交会成真
that can be sure you you you you you
那可以确保你你你你你
could take all the J mods that that ship
可以带走所有的J mod
in in in JDK 9 rewrite all of their
在JDK 9中重写了所有
module and fit class files to export
模块和适合类文件以导出
everything you could you could J link
您可能会做的所有事情J链接
that into your own image and you could
变成你自己的形象，你可以
access everything all the time and is it
一直访问所有内容，是吗
a good practice to well in in fact we we
一个很好的实践，实际上我们
do have some integrity checks in the J
在J中确实进行了一些完整性检查
in the J mods for the JDK that we record
在我们记录的JDK的J mods中
a strong hash of each one in the J mod
J mod中每个人的强哈希
for the base module so the so that is a
对于基本模块，因此，这是一个
it's actually very difficult to spoof
其实很难欺骗
the built in modules if you if you're if
内置模块（如果您）
you're going to link them we're but
您将要链接它们，我们只是
we're not doing any public key
我们没有做任何公钥
cryptography or signing or any of that
密码学或签名或任何
stuff it's it's it's you know it gets
东西是它是你知道它得到
very cumbersome and the and it doesn't
非常麻烦，并且它不会
seem worth the trouble
似乎值得麻烦
that isn't that is an interesting thing
那不是一件有趣的事
that we we haven't considered we could
我们没有考虑过我们可以
we could bake into the VM the hash of
我们可以将VM的哈希值烘烤到VM中
the base model itself and that and that
基本模型本身以及那个和那个
would prevent this sort of thing it
会阻止这种事情
wouldn't Britain sorry it wouldn't
英国不会后悔
prevent it you can always get the source
阻止它，您总是可以获取源
code and build it all yourself but it
自己编写代码并进行构建
would it would discourage people from
会阻止人们
rampantly rewriting the module infos
猖re地重写模块信息